Guide to the Yale Co-operative Corporation Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale Co-operative Corporation records
1981-1998
RU 921
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
9.25
(7 boxes)
The records consist of minutes, correspondence, legal agreements, contracts, scrapbooks and albums, and printed material documenting the operations and bankruptcy of the Yale Co-op.
Yale Co-operative Corporation
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 37 (YRG 37), Records of associations, institutes, centers, and organizations affiliated with Yale.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred by the former officers of the Yale co-operative Corporation, 2002.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of minutes, correspondence, legal agreements, contracts, scrapbooks and albums, and printed material documenting the operations and bankruptcy of the Yale Co-op.
College stores; Yale Co-operative Corporation
- Records ot the Yale Co-operative Corporation, circa 1981-1998; Accession 2003-A-062
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2033
  - Advertisement albums
    - 1986-1987 (Box 1)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 1)
    - 1989-1991 (Box 1)
    - 1993 (Box 1)
    - 1995 (Box 1)
    - 1997-1998 (Box 1)
    - 1989-1990, inserts (Box 2)
    - 1989-1997 (Box 2)
    - 1995 (Box 2)
    - 1996-1997 (Box 2)
    - 1997 (Box 2)
  - Catalog re-caps, 1990-1997
  - Handbook from Wallace Bookstores, Inc., 1995
  - Ephemera
  - Agreements, contracts, leases, circa 1983-1999 (Box 3)
  - Depreciation schedules (Box 3)
  - Leases (Box 4)
  - Nominations, elections (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 1995- (Box 4)
  - Minutes (Box 4)
  - CNT notes (Box 4)
  - Merchandise committee (Box 4)
  - Customer survey (Box 4)
  - Ad. Lit. (Box 4)
  - Ad Hoc Committee (Box 4)
  - Union contracts (Box 4)
  - Book Committee (Box 4)
  - Special Olympics (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 1995- (Box 5)
  - Board of directors lists (Box 5)
  - Board agendas (Box 5)
  - Finance Committee (Box 5)
  - Budget deliberations (Box 5)
  - Correspondence and meetings (Box 5)
  - Barnes and Noble negotiations, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Audit Committee (Box 5)
  - Board meeting, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Board meeting, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Chapel Square Mall lease negotiations (Box 7)
  - Chapel Square Mall correspondence (Box 7)
  - Lease negotiation, 1996 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence re: lease (Box 7)
  - Profit sharing agreement (Box 7)
  - Coursebook registration letters (Box 7)
  - Co-op relocation (Box 7)
  - State funding (Box 7)
  - Employment agreements (Box 7)
  - Financial analyses (Box 7)
  - Barnes and Noble letters (Box 7)
  - Marketing letters (Box 7)
  - Assorted (Box 7)